NO, NO HERE'S
MY OTHER QUESTION.
YEAH SEPTIC.
TELL ME YEAH,
I WAS WANT
TO DO THE
ONE FOR THE
HOUSE IS ONLY
A THOUSAND YEAH,
I'LL TELL YOU
YEAH, SO IT'S
I'M THINKING ABOUT
UPGRADING AND THEN
HITTING ON TO
CORRECT.
IS THERE A
SETBACK?
FROM MAXIMUM AS
FAR AS THAT
GOES BECAUSE I'M
MAXIMUM DISTANCE NO,
THERE'S NO MAXIMUM
DISTANCE.
THE THING WE'LL
RUN INTO IS
PITCH THAT WE
HIRE WHERE WE'RE
GOING TO MAKE
THE PITCH RIGHT
NOW WE CAN
GO REALLY LOW
ON THE PITCH
IF WE USE
A SIX INCH
PIPE.
OKAY, SO WE
CAN GET DOWN
TO UH TWO
PERCENT.
OKAY, WHICH IS
UH A LITTLE
OVER AN EIGHTH
OF AN INCH
PER FOOT IF
WE USE SIX
INCH YES, WELL
WE CAN DO
IT 100% BUT
THE SECRET TO
THAT IS WE
GOT TO MAKE
SURE THAT PIPE'S
PERFECT SO WOULD
YOU TAKE CARE
OF THE ENGINEERING?
OH EVERYTHING.
YEAH.
YEAH NEW OLD
STUFF.
CORRECT YEAH,